Bryant Baumgartner

IT Graduate

Information technology graduate with coursework and experience in software development and database management. Successful in IT best-practices and problem solving using various computer environments. Strong desire to create high quality software within a development team.

Education

2017-08 -2021-05 **Bachelor of Science: Information Technology**

Saint Martin's University - Lacey, WA

 Relevant Coursework Completed: Data Structures and Algorithms & Database Management

Work History

2022-01 -2022-02 Java SDET Trainee

Mthree, United States

- Used Spring Boot and JDBC to develop Rest applications.
- Worked with teammates to construct a React Web App.
- Covered Java and SQL techniques using Apache Netbeans and MS SQL Server.

2018-08 -2019-01

Front End

Haggen Food & Pharmacy, Stanwood, Washington

- Provided high quality customer service.
- Trained new team members.
- Handled money transfers and some store operations.

Contact

Address

Stanwood, WA, 98292

Phone

(425) 320-8501

E-mail

bryant.baumgartner@gmail .com

Skills

C# .NET, Unity



HTML, CSS, PHP and JavaScript



MySQL, T-SQL



Java



Database management



Python



Git

